[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Five packs of Seven Stars.
We don't sell Seven Stars.
Ten packs of Seven Stars.
Is seven packs okay?
Two packs are enough.
Hey, stop!
You said you didn't steal.
So why did you run so fast?
Who knew what you wanted to do? Why did you falsely accuse me?
You were being shady. I had my eye on you.
Aunt, just now I saw that he--
Are you blind?
Go watch the door.
What?
I only found 200 bucks on him.
What are you looking at?
You can't even keep watch.
What a waste of money raising you was.
If your mom hadn't died, who would've taken on a burden like you?
That deadpan face of yours just annoys me.
Hey.
I know you're coming back for it after closing.
I took 3,000 bucks as my commission.
Where are you? Did you vanish while on watch?
I went to the store. Didn't your side piece want food?
Do you have a death wish?
Watch your mouth.
Get your ass back here now.
Make a sound, and you'll die.
THE FIXERS
DOG EAT DOG
Madam Fan is asking for me.
Dead or vanished,
the client doesn't care,
as long as it is taken care of.
Okay.
Madam Fan.
I heard it was an older man and a younger man.
Yes. They had the same goal as us.
Maybe there was a problem on the client's end.
I'll handle it.
Something was taken from me during the mission.
I want to get it back.
Your necklace.
Who was it from?
I've never seen you without it.
It's the only thing my family left me.
All the more reason to get it back.
Go home first.
Wait until you hear from me before you act on the case.
Okay.
Tai.
Tai, the director general is done picking.
X: DID YOU DELETE ALL THE VIDEOS ON YOUR END?
Next, the tragedy that has shocked the entertainment industry.
An explicit video of pop star Sheng went viral.
FIXER GOLD
Stop it.
…was used to dox her…
Sweet and sour ribs again?
However, it appears she struggled…
Didn't I tell you to call me instead of showing up at my office?
But you didn't answer my call.
I'm a poor dad, man. Gotta make money.
No time for your calls.
Why are we seeing this four-eyes?
Sir, who are you?
Wear your reading glasses, or your eyes will go bad.
I don't need them.
I need you to look into a few scumbags for us.
Can't you wait till I get off work and take my kid home?
Dude, what time do you get off work?
We need the case closed tomorrow.
That will be tough. I want a 40% cut.
Damn. Are you exploiting us?
Dude, raising a kid costs a lot.
And I need laser eye surgery.
Fine, 40%.
Hold on.
Fuck, you have a kid, and I don't?
40% is so steep.
It's coming from your portion.
I want you to look into this account called Tai.
Sheng asked him via DM if the videos were deleted.
That means he has Sheng's self-recorded videos.
Maybe he leaked them.
Shit.
My manager is calling. Time to code.
Hey, help me clean up.
I'll tell you what I find.
I'll pay the 40%.
You clean up.
Fuck, talk about being damn broke.
He got a drink and didn't even touch it.
Hey.
I have two questions for you.
Why do you have so many questions?
What?
We've already deleted Ms. Yen's daughter's videos.
Why are we still investigating?
Sheng's videos still got leaked.
We have to find out who posted them.
Okay.
Teach the scumbag a lesson.
That four-eyes won't find anything this soon, right?
Fixer Stealth is Ching He's best intelligence support.
What?
Slacking off on your first mission already?
No.
My son just finished his midterms.
I promised to treat him to a nice meal tonight.
It's okay. We can have it another day.
Where are we heading next? Let's roll.
He probably won't find anything this soon.
Go ahead.
Are you messing with me?
Hey, it's not that easy to lose me, all right?
Hey, keep your phone on.
Be ready once we get the intel. Got it?
Fee-fi-fo-fum!
Thank you.
Hey, what was your second question?
What comes after "Roses are red, violets are blue"?
"I'll take you down a peg or two," fool!
SWAMP EEL NOODLES
What's with the feast?
My son came in first.
We gotta celebrate.
Amazing.
-Great job. -Thank you.
It's just midterms. You act like I got into my dream school.
Your dad said the gambling house has been doing great.
He suddenly gave me over 100 grand. God knows from where.
I've been lucky lately.
And the gambling house is packed.
I'm too busy to even call you.
Really? If the business is that good, how about this?
Help me stock up on seafood to sell?
-Dad, what's wrong? -What?
Why is your hand shaking?
Is it?
An occupational injury.
I shake the dice cup every day.
It's become a reflex now. Give it a few days.
I'm being serious here.
Why don't you schedule a full health checkup?
You know my customer, Old Hsiao?
He recently did a checkup and was diagnosed with sarcopenia.
He has trouble even walking.
Are you crazy?
That Old Hsiao is over 70 years old. Don't compare me to him.
I'm worried about you.
Hey, don't let these two sit. We must finish them.
We can box whatever's left.
As if we need you to tell us. Also, this needs to be eaten first.
All right, you're the smartest.
-Hey, eat more. -Okay.
Keep it up next year.
Don't make it sound so easy.
It's so easy for you.
-No. -It is.
I study a lot.
You're my son.
I just got raided a while ago. I've already done my best.
Make up for it next time.
Give it to me.
Give it to me. Hurry up.
Found the phone yet?
As if that's possible.
You want me to go to the police?
Of course not.
I'm just wondering if there's any evidence of me on the phone.
What's this?
I'm in trouble, and you make it about you?
What are we? You think I'd only care about myself?
We've worked together how long? Hasn't it been great?
I still need your help getting clients.
Once things die down, it'll all be good, okay?
The leak? Who the fuck cares, man? People will forget about it.
That girl died.
All the sponsors are pulling out.
It's not just about the bad press, okay?
That girl's death isn't your fault, okay?
You only filmed it. You didn't distribute it, okay?
Whoever did that, hey, had a fucking conscience.
They blurred her face.
Do you have more?
Give me some more.
If cops question you, remember not to say my name.
You've been doing this for over ten years.
You still handle
every case personally.
This client went to Yeh Yueh Tong behind our back.
Something feels off.
When you meet them later, keep an eye out.
If Fixer Lunar knew
that you weren't coming and were only sending me,
she would feel insulted.
You've been with Ching He the longest.
You have the most seniority.
Why should she feel insulted?
Besides, you still call her Fixer Lunar.
That is showing her plenty of respect.
After such a long time, I've gotten used to it.
I mean nothing by it.
It's just like how sometimes, when I see you,
the name Fixer Solar comes to mind.
I didn't know the rules between you two, so I hired both of you.
It's okay.
I know you love your daughter dearly.
There is always an order to things.
Prosecutor, may I ask
who you commissioned first?
Ching He.
However, first doesn't always mean best.
That applies to cases and positions.
Don't you agree, Sir Hong?
The videos filmed by those scumbags are starting to leak.
I don't know if my daughter's will be next.
You said
you'd handle it, even if you had to kill.
I don't care if you're competitors.
You got paid, so you have to get the job done.
Work together or not,
I just want my daughter to be safe.
Please.
Although Yeh Yueh Tong and Ching He have never worked together,
if it means completing the job faster,
I don't mind making an exception.
The Tai account belongs to someone named Cho Wen-tai.
He owns a nightclub called Ash.
I restored a conversation between Sheng and him.
Cho Wen-tai's been selling drugs to him. They mentioned many celebrities too.
But this isn't even the craziest part.
Sheng would bring Cho Wen-tai girls to drug at the nightclub.
Seems like this is just the tip of the iceberg.
Before we continue,
something needs to be clarified.
Ching He just found out
that three years ago, your daughter
was hospitalized after falling into a coma.
It was impossible for her to have filmed a video with Sheng.
Ms. Yen, what exactly is the purpose of this job?
Here to investigate Cho Wen-tai too?
Give it back to me.
Did you come for the case or your thing?
Both.
You should've told me then.
Too bad I didn't bring it.
Why don't you tell me how you'll approach Cho Wen-tai?
The same way you approached Sheng?
Mission canceled.
SIR HONG: MISSION CANCELED
The job has been canceled.
Stand down.
Why?
The client lied.
Her target is Cho Wen-tai.
Cho Wen-tai sells drugs and colludes with scumbags like Sheng
to drug and rape girls.
But he's always released for lack of evidence.
Tai.
There's even pressure from higher-ups to stop investigating.
Did you see that chick with her hair in buns dancing wildly?
Oh, yes.
Take her to the VIP room.
Okay.
-Hey. -So…
Not the two ugly ones.
…your goal is to make us investigate Cho Wen-tai,
not delete the videos.
Am I correct?
These people hurt my daughter.
I can't let them go unpunished.
Using both Yeh Yueh Tong and Ching He to do your policing.
How amusing.
Ching He is canceling this job right now.
You will be fully refunded.
Didn't you also see
what Cho Wen-tai did?
Fixers aren't your tools for solving cases.
No matter how atrocious Cho Wen-tai's actions are,
they have nothing to do with us.
Since Ching He is pulling out,
I'm pulling out too.
I don't take cases they don't want.
You posted
the female model's video online, didn't you?
Yes.
If I hadn't done that,
those scumbags' misdeeds would forever be covered up.
No one would've known.
And no one would've cared.
Do you think
sacrificing a girl like that
is worth it?
If sacrificing one person
can prevent further harm…
then it's worth it.
That's it? We're letting him go?
Fixer Gold,
the job has been canceled.
Whatever you do next will be on you.
-Hello? -Done with dinner?
Obviously. Look at the time.
Come to the address I sent you.
And remember every single word I say next.
Dad, what are you doing?
Why are you awake at this hour?
I'm doing practice problems.
Didn't exams just end?
The unified exam is coming up. I have no time.
Bud, if you keep this up, your body will give out in half a year.
Yours is the one giving out.
Mom told you to get a checkup, and you keep stalling.
The time has come.
Your old man has to take a dump.
Finally, after being constipated for so long?
Hey, what were you saying?
Remember to get a checkup.
Being funny, are you?
Sheng, once a darling of the music scene, highly sought after by major brands,
has now become a hot potato.
A well-known mobile phone brand announced today
that it is officially ending all partnerships with Sheng
and removing all ads from public spaces and online.
Apart from existing contracts,
three brands that were negotiating with Sheng
reportedly backed out due to the scandal.
Falling from superstardom, Sheng…
BREAD AND CAKES
Fuck, so heavy, goddamn it!
Sorry, you can't enter here.
Who are you?
Someone gave me five million
to kill you.
Who?
Who wants to kill me?
Someone gave me five million to kill you.
I don't talk for free.
If you want to know something,
you need to pay the price.
Eight million. Who exactly wants to kill me?
Cho Wen-tai.
Sheng.
He said you know too much.
He said you leaked his sex videos.
He wants you silent.
What sex videos? Are you crazy?
What do you mean?
You're under scrutiny now.
You might spill everything when the cops take you in.
Bastard. Fucking kicking away the ladder?
Don't bother yelling.
No one will come.
Sorry, I'm just doing what I'm paid to do.
Wait!
I'll pay you double. Go kill him.
That's how much? How d'ya want it done?
I'll pay you ten million.
I don't care how Cho Wen-tai dies.
Who did you say wants me dead? Sheng?
I don't believe you.
Sheng doesn't have the guts.
Who wants to kill me?
We killers have a habit
in case the client goes back on their word.
I'll pay you ten million. I don't care how Cho Wen-tai dies.
Hello?
He's next to me.
Fuck, I'm about to.
Fuck you, Cho Wen-tai!
What? Fuck, are you kidding me? You're haggling now?
Fuck, I'm out!
Fuck you!
Not gonna touch you now.
Motherfucker, going back on his word.
He wanted to haggle. Said it was too pricey.
-Where is he? -In the nightclub office.
Wait, how much did you just offer?
I won't go back on my word.
Good.
Is this yours?
Yes. Why?
Here, have some.
Feel a little better.
Here.
Hello?
Okay.
He wants to see you.
You leaked my videos and wanted to kill me!
You think I didn't hear your offer?
Fuck!
Think I didn't hear your recording?
I got you so many chicks!
You fucking put a hit on me?
Which drugged girl haven't you screwed?
How would you have gotten the goods without me?
They're really going at it.
Hello? I want to report a crime.
There's a fight at Ash nightclub.
Hey, what was going through your head?
How did you come up with this?
This is Fixer Shadow's favorite method.
Tried and tested.
Back in the day, things were simpler.
Better to get on a brother's wrong side than a fixer's.
By the way, how is Fixer Shadow doing now?
You shot him. What do you think?
All right. I'm really sorry.
I'll apologize sometime, okay?
The job was canceled.
Don't tell me you had nothing to do with them going at each other's throats.
I just wanted to confirm that our plan could go smoothly.
Although Cho Wen-tai is a scumbag,
I'm warning you not to break the rules again.
And from now on, your code name
is Fixer Lucky, as in good luck.
Fixer Lucky? How auspicious.
Hey, did you hear that?
-Fixer Lucky. -Fixer Bottom.
Did I pass my probationary period?
Go home and rest first.
When there is a new case,
I will notify you.
Young man, you couldn't stand Cho Wen-tai's actions, could you?
It's none of your business.
Damn.
There you go again.
You're difficult, seriously.
So handsome, but such an awful temper.
What a waste, seriously.
Sheng, whose explicit video was leaked, is involved in another scandal.
A video of him fighting with nightclub tycoon Cho Wen-tai
went viral online today.
The 120-second exchange
raised eyebrows with mentions of drugging and drug dealing…
Hey, Fixer Stealth.
I'm sending you a photo.
Look into that woman for me.
Don't pull out your weapon.
It ruins the peace.
Are you gonna talk?
Gerald Chen came to me for help.
He barely spoke when he got a call and rushed off.
I didn't hear from him afterward.
Who called?
Don't tell anyone I said this.
It was San He's boss,
Lin Wan-li.
Last time,
our ship came in with cargo
and got searched.
Did we calm the crew?
Sorry, boss. I'm not sure.
Pin is handling all of this.
SAN HE BATHHOUSE
Have you seen this person?
No.
This coin is only found here.
Have you really never?
Many people come here.
How can I remember?
BEN
Who are you to her?
A friend.
When are you meeting her?
A man like you,
looking for a woman this way, what do you want?
-Keep watch. -Okay.
How many times must I say it?
I'll handle that load myself.
Do you understand?
And then?
Hsiu?
Do you follow my orders or his?
Fucking hell, ridiculous.
Pin.
You are a capable person,
but capability alone isn't enough.
Hsiu's experience
can save you a lot of trouble.
If you can't control your temper,
you can't control your men.
San He will eventually be handed over to you two.
Harmony comes first.
Should I tell men to see you out,
my brother?
No need.
Again? Damn. Enough.
What? Look over there.
-Stupid. -All right.
-Do you want-- -That burns!
How old are you guys?
Who?
Shit, it's boss.
-Hello, boss. I'm 20. -Hello, boss. I'm 18.
Remember.
The brothers you meet
at your age
are your true brothers.
Don't argue or fall out so easily.
-Got it? -Okay.
Boss, we'll see you out.
Again with seeing me out?
What's going on?
I'm dying, is that it?
Everyone wants to see me out.
No, boss.
-Sorry, boss. -Sorry, boss.
He should be a fixer too, right?
Is he your partner?
Let him go.
Why should I,
Mina Shen?
"Mina Shen. Lost both parents at a young age."
"Raised by an aunt, who ran a gambling den."
Are you blind?
"Consistently excelled at school."
"Studied chemical engineering." Goodness.
You were a top student.
I don't need you
to tell me who I am.
Why are you always in my way?
Who is harassing whom now?
Yeh Yueh Tong keeps blocking Ching He.
Ching He certainly has to pay a visit.
Is that all?
Did you come… to warn me
or to see me?
I came to warn you.
And to see you. What about it?
I already told him that I'm a friend.
Still got treated as an enemy.
I just wanted to return this.
Give it back to me.
Don't get in my way again.
I left money for your treatment. Bye.
Fuck. Ching He discovered your identity.
-If Yeh Yueh Tong knows-- -It's fine.
This is a personal feud.
I say, you should stop investigating.
If Gerald doesn't want to be found,
no amount of searching will help.
I have a feeling
I will find him soon.
I have to go.
Already? In such a rush?
Apply your ointment.
Gosh, young people these days…
What a mess.
Damn, if I weren't crippled,
that fellow would've been on the floor.
At least
I got some US dollars.
Make a sound, and you will die.
Give me the phone.
I don't want to kill you.
But he will.
I'm going to lower the knife.
Just leave quietly.
You didn't see anything.
If you run your mouth,
I'll use this phone to find you and your family.
You won't be the only one in trouble.
Thank you.
Where do you want the body this time?
Put it in that woman's room.
When she wakes up and sees it, she'll spill everything.
Nah. I gotta say this even if we're buds.
I'm charging this time.
This is turning into your body disposal plant.
Is Yeh Yueh Tong paying you too little? Should I talk to Madam Fan?
Fuck you.
Do you want me to die?
Let's get going.
Give me back my phone.
Lower your gun. I'll handle it.
If I lose my phone,
I'll be beaten to death.
What did you see earlier?
You borrowed my phone
and forgot to return it.
So I came for it.
I didn't see anything else.
If I give you back your phone,
how do I know that you won't recall something?
By the alley,
there are tokens and blood.
Don't forget them.
Hold it up so I can see it better.
How old are you?
Sixteen.
What were you doing at 16?
At 16?
-I don't even remember 36. -Teach me.
Teach me how to shoot.
Do you know what we do?
You're gonna use the body in the trunk
to threaten someone.
Didn't you say you saw nothing?
If I become an accomplice,
it won't matter whether I saw anything.
Right?
The girl is quite a natural.
Clean up the blood you saw.
Are you gonna talk?
Gerald Chen came to me for help.
He barely spoke when he got a call and rushed off.
Who called?
It was San He's boss,
Lin Wan-li.
Hello?
My beautiful wife.
I just bought food and am heading home.
Should I get anything for you?
Okay.
Subtitle translation by: